<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Religion on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</title>
    <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/tags/religion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Religion on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/tags/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Convenient Doctrines</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/convenient-doctrines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/convenient-doctrines/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most people have wondered at times at the number of strange and contradictory doctrines that circle the globe in the name of God. Religion is a mass of conflicting statements, a jungle too dense for most educated people these days to even consider seeking refuge in it. As soon as we become smart enough to examine even two churches or religions side by side, we see enough contradictions to know that they cannot both be right. And by the time that we have been through three or four, a doubt begins to grow that any of them could be right.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head Coverings</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/headcoverings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/headcoverings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There have been whole denominations that have split over varying interpretations of one chapter of the Bible, which is: 1 Corinthians 11. This is the chapter that deals with women covering their heads when they pray.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kingdom of Heaven or Religion</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-kingdom-of-heaven-or-religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-kingdom-of-heaven-or-religion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We wanted to know the important differences between the Christian religion and all other religions; between the part of the Bible before Jesus was born, and the part after he was born, between the teachings of Jesus and the teachings of all other religious leaders. We were not interested in the small differences that most people argue about. We asked God to show us the important differences, and he did.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
