<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Inspirational on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/categories/inspirational/</link><description>Recent content in Inspirational on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/categories/inspirational/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Letter From A Backslider</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/a-letter-from-a-backslider/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/a-letter-from-a-backslider/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Study to show yourself approved unto God, a workman that needeth not to be ashamed, rightly dividing the word of truth.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;a href="http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=2&amp;#43;Timothy&amp;#43;2%3A15;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print"


 title="Read 2 Timothy 2:15"



 target="_blank"
 


&gt;2 Timothy 2:15&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Buying Time</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/redeem-the-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/redeem-the-time/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Time is life. When you give your time to a person or thing, you are giving your life. When you &amp;ldquo;kill time&amp;rdquo;, you are destroying your life. When you use time well, you are using your life well.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hope</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/hope/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/hope/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I went to a church meeting yesterday, and the Bible reading was the Old Testament promise that God would not allow one of his righteous servants so much as to stub his toe against a stone. If he fell, the passage promised that God would send an angel to catch him. The congregation did not appear to see any contradiction (or even a connection) in the fact that the reading was preceded by an announcement that the pastor was not there because he had fallen off the back of his ute, and broken his wrist pretty badly. Apart from the obvious humour of that situation, there was the oft ignored contradiction that some of the things we read in the Bible do not seem to measure up to our everyday experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Great Escape</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/the-great-escape/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/the-great-escape/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a difficult story to tell, and that probably explains why it has taken some fifteen years for us to get around to telling it. The difficult part is not telling the story, but the difficult part is the fact that we have always shied away from giving testimonies about miracles, because of what the Bible says about evil people wanting miracles and not being content just less sensational truth. We also know that it can be somewhat discouraging to hear miraculous accounts from other Christians when our own lives seem so unexciting by comparison. We should start by saying that this story is probably one of the top three stories of God&amp;rsquo;s provision over a period of 35 years of Christian service. (Maybe one day we will get around to telling the other two!)&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Revolution</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/the-revolution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/the-revolution/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a Bible study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please look up the verses.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Slippery Slope</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/the-slippery-slope/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/the-slippery-slope/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;We had a discussion last night and Jeremy rightly said, &amp;ldquo;I can see an article coming from this.&amp;rdquo;  We were discussing the concept of a  &amp;ldquo;slippery slope&amp;rdquo; in our Christian walk, and we came up with a number of interesting observations.  The argument I am referring to is the one that says a certain action or teaching is likely to lead to much worse actions.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>