<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guidance on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/tags/guidance/</link><description>Recent content in Guidance on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/tags/guidance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bottom Squeezers</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/bottom-squezing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/bottom-squezing/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Some of us squeeze toothpaste from the middle, and some squeeze it from the bottom. Bottom squeezers would like the world to follow their example; but middle squeezers argue that such obsession with order infringes on their spontaneous individuality.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Buying Time</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/redeem-the-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/redeem-the-time/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Time is life. When you give your time to a person or thing, you are giving your life. When you &amp;ldquo;kill time&amp;rdquo;, you are destroying your life. When you use time well, you are using your life well.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Character</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/character/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/character/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;What ever happened to good old-fashioned character?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world is full of friendly, polite, helpful&amp;hellip; outwardly very nice people. But in the midst of adversity, when &amp;rsquo;niceness&amp;rsquo; is really needed, how much remains?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Eight Ways to Know God's Will</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/eight-ways-to-know-gods-will/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/eight-ways-to-know-gods-will/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There is nothing particularly &amp;lsquo;Quakerish&amp;rsquo; about this article, except as it could relate to the concept of silent worship, where Friends believe that God can speak to people.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Job List, Budgets, and Schedules</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/jobs-list-budgets-and-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/jobs-list-budgets-and-schedules/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;One of the best inventions in history must be that of daily schedules. Wristwatches (especially, cheap wristwatches) must be the next best invention. They made it possible for virtually everyone to co-ordinate their various schedules, so that people could arrange to be in the same place at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Learning To See</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/learning-to-see/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/learning-to-see/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="part-one"&gt;Part One&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;If the people cannot see where they are going, they will die.&amp;rdquo; (&lt;a href="http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=Proverbs&amp;#43;29%3A18;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print"


 title="Read Proverbs 29:18"



 target="_blank"
 


&gt;Proverbs 29:18&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>So, You Want to Start Your Own Ministry?</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/you-want-to-start-your-own-ministry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/you-want-to-start-your-own-ministry/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;People often write to us who are not satisfied with what they see in the churches today, and so they want to start their own ministry.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Space Without Spice</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/space-without-spice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/space-without-spice/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This article is a continuation of a topic which has been coming up a lot in the past couple of years. It deals with the dilemma that exists when a leader (or the community as a whole) encounters someone who shows some good spiritual signs, but who also shows an unwillingness to deal with some particular weakness or fault. Our traditional approach has been to take a grievance with the offender, and to advance the grievance from first stage to second, to third, and finally to kick them out of the community if they continue their refusal to deal with the offence. The process is scriptural and beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Teach Others To Teach Others</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/teach-others-to-teach-others/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/teach-others-to-teach-others/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Study to show yourself approved unto God, a workman that needeth not to be ashamed, rightly dividing the word of truth.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;a href="http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=2&amp;#43;Timothy&amp;#43;2%3A15;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print"


 title="Read 2 Timothy 2:15"



 target="_blank"
 


&gt;2 Timothy 2:15&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Slippery Slope</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/the-slippery-slope/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/the-slippery-slope/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;We had a discussion last night and Jeremy rightly said, &amp;ldquo;I can see an article coming from this.&amp;rdquo;  We were discussing the concept of a  &amp;ldquo;slippery slope&amp;rdquo; in our Christian walk, and we came up with a number of interesting observations.  The argument I am referring to is the one that says a certain action or teaching is likely to lead to much worse actions.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The True Conscience</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/the-true-conscience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/the-true-conscience/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: The term &amp;ldquo;social conscience&amp;rdquo; as used in this article has a different meaning (within the Jesus Christian community) to that which it normally has in society. We are talking about giving in to pressure from society to behave in certain ways which may actually be contrary to what a genuine conscience might teach us. An example of this would be social pressure to participate in war, which can make a sincere conscientious objector feel &amp;ldquo;guilty&amp;rdquo; for not conforming. We are NOT referring to &amp;ldquo;social conscience&amp;rdquo; in the way it is normally used (i.e. to feel a need to help others who are in need). That kind of social conscience is something with which we would agree.It has struck me that I must have failed somewhere in my attempts to teach people to recognise and follow what we call our conscience.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Try The Spirits</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/try-the-spirits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/try-the-spirits/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(This study is written in Easy English.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are many times when we must judge other people, and say if we believe they are right or if we believe they are wrong.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>We're Right They're Wrong</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/were-right-theyre-wrong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/were-right-theyre-wrong/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Within our community, we try to use the Golden Rule &amp;ndash; measuring our actions by the same principles that we use for measuring the actions of our enemies, and vice versa. So if, for example, we want freedom to distribute our literature, then we believe that they should have the same freedom. If it is wrong for them to cause division in our ranks, then we must not deliberately set out to cause division in their ranks. And so on and so on.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Wisdom</title><link>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/wisdom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://MgaKristiyanongHesus.github.io/en/blog/wisdom/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A number of children&amp;rsquo;s stories tell of someone getting one or more wishes, and then wasting them on things that do not bring happiness. As a boy I had heard the story of Solomon being given a wish by God. (&lt;a href="http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=2&amp;#43;Chronicles&amp;#43;1%3A7-12;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print"


 title="Read 2 Chronicles 1:7-12"



 target="_blank"
 


&gt;2 Chronicles 1:7-12&lt;/a&gt;) It was not so different from the fairy tales, except that this one had a ring of truth about it. What a privilege it would have been to be given a wish by God! And how clever of Solomon to have asked for wisdom.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>