<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Endtime and Sex Issues on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</title>
    <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/categories/endtime-and-sex-issues/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Endtime and Sex Issues on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/categories/endtime-and-sex-issues/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Endtime Prophecy and The Revelation of Jesus Christ</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/endtime-prophesy-and-revelation-of-jesus-christ/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/endtime-prophesy-and-revelation-of-jesus-christ/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The prophecies contained in the books of Daniel, Revelation, and the Gospels have many levels, each of which is valid; but only if approached from a sincere desire to know and obey the truth. The Revelation is an integral part of the whole message of God in the Bible, and the key to understanding the book of Revelation is the teachings of Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God&#39;s Kingdom</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-kingdom-of-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-kingdom-of-god/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is one phrase which seems to sum up the very essence of the link between the Gospels and The Revelation, and that is the phrase I have used as the title for this article.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living In Community</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/living-in-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/living-in-community/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have always believed that living in community (as we do, and as the early Christians did) is somewhat optional. It is not commanded (in so many words) in what Jesus taught, although he and his disciples obviously lived together, travelled together, and had a common purse. I have felt strongly about the spiritual benefits of such a lifestyle; but I just didn&amp;rsquo;t think there was a case for making it absolutely essential.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May Your Kingdom Come</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/may-your-kingdom-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/may-your-kingdom-come/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As people with a serious concern for the welfare of this planet, the return of Christ offers us hope.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Servants of The Antichrist</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/slaves-of-the-antichrist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/slaves-of-the-antichrist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Left Behind&lt;/em&gt; series is inspiring, in that it makes people think about serious, life-and-death situations. Yet it tends to assume that, even in the face of disaster, life for fundamentalist American Christians will center around the same values and goals that have dominated their lives up until now. In other words, people will still go to church on Sundays and work in system jobs the rest of the week, right through the Tribulation and all that comes with it. They will still be loaded with money, and they will still jet around the world at will. There is nothing in the book that speaks to the condition of poor Christians. This materialistic philosophy is practised at a time (in the story) when people should be seriously considering whether the values they lived by before the trouble began were really the right ones.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Sense</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/sexs-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/sexs-sense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Opinions, experiences, customs, and beliefs about sex differ so much that almost nothing can be said dogmatically on the subject. Yet this is an area where dogmas abound&amp;hellip; from restrictive religious dogmas to permissive liberal dogmas (e.g. &amp;ldquo;Nothing is wrong if it makes you feel good&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs of The Times</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/signs-of-the-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/signs-of-the-times/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;War and Peace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wars are the most common proof given that the end of the world is near. Yet they are mentioned specifically by Christ as proof that the end has not come: &amp;ldquo;You will hear of wars and rumours of wars. Do not let this trouble you, for all these things must happen, but the end is not yet.&amp;rdquo; (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=Matthew&amp;#43;24%3A6;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read Matthew 24:6&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;Matthew 24:6&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gift of Prophesy</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-gift-of-prophesy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-gift-of-prophesy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some concerns are more understandable, and more honest, than others. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hollywood Scam</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-hollywood-deception/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-hollywood-deception/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-hollywood-scam&#34;&gt;The Hollywood Scam&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://jesuschristians.com/images/Article_pics/Article_Intro_Pics/Endtime_and_Sex/The_Hollywood_Scam.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It has been about forty years since Hollywood first took the leap into nude sex scenes in movies, and it may be time to look back on how that has influenced our thinking about such things.  I am going to argue in this article that many of us have been coyed into believing that there was something right and good about the decision to incorporate nude sex scenes into mass entertainment, when, in fact, it actually exposed (and continues to expose) us as naive suckers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Intuition Myth</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-intuition-myth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-intuition-myth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a term that I have heard for many years and just kind of assumed I was missing something when I heard it. The word is intuition. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how it has been used in the past, but I know that I mostly hear it used when comparing males and females. Females are told that they have intuitive skills, or that they think intuitively, whereas men think in some other way, e.g. rationally. Unless I&amp;rsquo;ve missed something, it always seemed to imply two things, both of which I would like to challenge in this article: (1) that intuition is some kind of a skill; and (2) that women have some kind of a special claim on this skill.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Love of Selfie</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-love-of-selfie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-love-of-selfie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;But know this, that in the last days perilous times will come: 2 For men will be lovers of themselves, lovers of money, boasters, proud, blasphemers, disobedient to parents, unthankful, unholy,&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=2&amp;#43;Timothy&amp;#43;3%3A2;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read 2 Timothy 3:2&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;2 Timothy 3:2&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mark of the Beast</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-mark-of-the-beast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-mark-of-the-beast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The last book of the Bible is called The Revelation by Protestants and The Apocalypse by Catholics. It is a poetic description of the battle between good and evil, using numerous symbols and creatures to illustrate its message.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
