<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Letter From A Backslider</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/a-letter-from-a-backslider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/a-letter-from-a-backslider/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Study to show yourself approved unto God, a workman that needeth not to be ashamed, rightly dividing the word of truth.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=2&amp;#43;Timothy&amp;#43;2%3A15;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read 2 Timothy 2:15&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;2 Timothy 2:15&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Letter to a Friend</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/a-letter-to-a-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/a-letter-to-a-friend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Jesus Christian approach to universalism (which is not the approach of any Australian Quakers that we know of apart from ourselves) is that Jesus somehow enabled God to provide universal salvation. Below is a letter we wrote to a conservative believer who challenged our claim that non-Christians may actually be saved through the blood of Christ (and the grace of God) as long as they are walking in all the light that they have.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Power Corrupts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/a-war-against-all-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/a-war-against-all-power/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Power tends to corrupt, and absolute power corrupts absolutely. Great men are almost always bad men.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/amazing-grace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/amazing-grace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is easy to assume that people have already heard about God&amp;rsquo;s grace through the churches. But on closer inspection, it appears that the churches themselves do not believe the gospel they preach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anarchy and Pacifism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/anarchy-and-pacifism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/anarchy-and-pacifism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Although the Jesus Christians have always been staunch pacifists, and although they are critical of religious hierarchies, in the article below, they examine weaknesses in their own position.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bottom Squeezers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/bottom-squezing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/bottom-squezing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some of us squeeze toothpaste from the middle, and some squeeze it from the bottom. Bottom squeezers would like the world to follow their example; but middle squeezers argue that such obsession with order infringes on their spontaneous individuality.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buying Time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/redeem-the-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/redeem-the-time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Time is life. When you give your time to a person or thing, you are giving your life. When you &amp;ldquo;kill time&amp;rdquo;, you are destroying your life. When you use time well, you are using your life well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Character</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/character/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/character/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What ever happened to good old-fashioned character?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The world is full of friendly, polite, helpful&amp;hellip; outwardly very nice people. But in the midst of adversity, when &amp;rsquo;niceness&amp;rsquo; is really needed, how much remains?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Science</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/christian-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/christian-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the book Life After Life, a doctor interviews hundreds of people who were clinically dead and then revived. He notes a number of patterns in their experiences. One of these patterns was a widespread conviction by many of these people as they were dying that what really matters in life is not how much money you earn, but how much you love others and how much you learn.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convenient Doctrines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/convenient-doctrines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/convenient-doctrines/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most people have wondered at times at the number of strange and contradictory doctrines that circle the globe in the name of God. Religion is a mass of conflicting statements, a jungle too dense for most educated people these days to even consider seeking refuge in it. As soon as we become smart enough to examine even two churches or religions side by side, we see enough contradictions to know that they cannot both be right. And by the time that we have been through three or four, a doubt begins to grow that any of them could be right.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight Ways to Know God&#39;s Will</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/eight-ways-to-know-gods-will/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/eight-ways-to-know-gods-will/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There is nothing particularly &amp;lsquo;Quakerish&amp;rsquo; about this article, except as it could relate to the concept of silent worship, where Friends believe that God can speak to people.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endtime Prophecy and The Revelation of Jesus Christ</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/endtime-prophesy-and-revelation-of-jesus-christ/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/endtime-prophesy-and-revelation-of-jesus-christ/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The prophecies contained in the books of Daniel, Revelation, and the Gospels have many levels, each of which is valid; but only if approached from a sincere desire to know and obey the truth. The Revelation is an integral part of the whole message of God in the Bible, and the key to understanding the book of Revelation is the teachings of Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fasting Without Ceasing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/fasting-without-ceasing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/fasting-without-ceasing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This kind goeth not out, except through prayer and fasting. (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=Matthew&amp;#43;17%3A14-21;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read Matthew 17:14-21&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;Matthew 17:14-21&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forsaking All</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/forsaking-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/forsaking-all/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When Jesus walked by the shores of Galilee, he called some fishermen who had just caught the biggest haul of their lives: &amp;ldquo;Come follow me and I will make you fishers of men!&amp;rdquo; Immediately they forsook all and followed him! (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=Luke&amp;#43;5%3A2-11;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read Luke 5:2-11&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;Luke 5:2-11&lt;/a&gt;) They forsook the fish, the nets, their boat, their livelihood, their old life, and even their poor old father!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forsaking Your Parents</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/forsaking-your-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/forsaking-your-family/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the reasons why we do not teach much about forsaking parents is because it is something that we just do in practical terms, more than we actually teach it in theoretical terms. We forsake our parents merely by living together communally, seven days a week. Young people who suddenly decide to join a community like our own (after having lived with their parents) &amp;ldquo;forsake&amp;rdquo; the relationship that they had at home as a natural consequence of choosing to move in with us. This is not terribly different from what happens when a young person leaves home to get married, move into a flat on their own, move into student accommodation at a university, or travel or work abroad.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freedom, Prayer, and Besetting Sins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/freedom-prayer-and-besetting-sins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/freedom-prayer-and-besetting-sins/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a few different thoughts I would like to share with people, each one probably worthy of a short article on its own. However, until or unless I get some spare time to do them as separate articles, I will just kind of mix them all in together in this letter, since there is a common theme between them. The theme is just an expression of concern about where people are heading spiritually, particularly in light of individual bases now being autonomous to one another.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God Has No Grandchildren</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/god-has-no-grandchildren/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/god-has-no-grandchildren/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We do not have to be perfect to be accepted by God. But we do need to be original.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God&#39;s Kingdom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-kingdom-of-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-kingdom-of-god/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is one phrase which seems to sum up the very essence of the link between the Gospels and The Revelation, and that is the phrase I have used as the title for this article.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head Coverings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/headcoverings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/headcoverings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There have been whole denominations that have split over varying interpretations of one chapter of the Bible, which is: 1 Corinthians 11. This is the chapter that deals with women covering their heads when they pray.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing What We Don&#39;t Want to Hear</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/hearing-what-we-dont-want-to-hear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/hearing-what-we-dont-want-to-hear/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What I want to say here is so basic that it&amp;rsquo;s almost a first requirement for faith. And yet it seems to be so rare (and so hard to communicate) that it hardly exists in the world today.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hope</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/hope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/hope/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I went to a church meeting yesterday, and the Bible reading was the Old Testament promise that God would not allow one of his righteous servants so much as to stub his toe against a stone. If he fell, the passage promised that God would send an angel to catch him. The congregation did not appear to see any contradiction (or even a connection) in the fact that the reading was preceded by an announcement that the pastor was not there because he had fallen off the back of his ute, and broken his wrist pretty badly. Apart from the obvious humour of that situation, there was the oft ignored contradiction that some of the things we read in the Bible do not seem to measure up to our everyday experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job List, Budgets, and Schedules</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/jobs-list-budgets-and-schedules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/jobs-list-budgets-and-schedules/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the best inventions in history must be that of daily schedules. Wristwatches (especially, cheap wristwatches) must be the next best invention. They made it possible for virtually everyone to co-ordinate their various schedules, so that people could arrange to be in the same place at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Say It</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/just-say-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/just-say-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There really is nothing wrong with what the &amp;ldquo;sinner&amp;rsquo;s prayer&amp;rdquo; says, even though we have tended to put it down in the past. And getting people to actually say the things that are said in the sinner&amp;rsquo;s prayer is a very good exercise. I just wish that we could get them to continue saying those things. Our complaint about the prayer is more that it tends to become a once-and-for-all ritual, that exempts people from continuing to grow in their faith.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning To See</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/learning-to-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/learning-to-see/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;part-one&#34;&gt;Part One&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;If the people cannot see where they are going, they will die.&amp;rdquo; (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=Proverbs&amp;#43;29%3A18;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read Proverbs 29:18&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;Proverbs 29:18&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living By Faith</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/live-by-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/live-by-faith/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the third in a series of articles on doctrinal differences between ourselves and The Family. The first two articles were &amp;ldquo;Simple Salvation&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Eternal Salvation&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living By Faith - And How to Do It</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/living-by-faith---and-how-to-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/living-by-faith---and-how-to-do-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jesus Christ taught people not to think about how to feed and clothe themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living In Community</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/living-in-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/living-in-community/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have always believed that living in community (as we do, and as the early Christians did) is somewhat optional. It is not commanded (in so many words) in what Jesus taught, although he and his disciples obviously lived together, travelled together, and had a common purse. I have felt strongly about the spiritual benefits of such a lifestyle; but I just didn&amp;rsquo;t think there was a case for making it absolutely essential.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May Your Kingdom Come</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/may-your-kingdom-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/may-your-kingdom-come/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As people with a serious concern for the welfare of this planet, the return of Christ offers us hope.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miracles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/miracles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/miracles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you understand how a miracle works, is it still a miracle? If I can do something you have no explanation for, does that make me spiritually superior to you? What is a miracle anyway? These are just a few of the questions which have perplexed me as I have tried to understand what my position should be with regard to the supernatural.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Love For Leftovers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/my-love-for-leftovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/my-love-for-leftovers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have often heard people complaining about having to eat &amp;ldquo;leftovers&amp;rdquo;. It baffles me, because it is said as though there is something inferior about leftovers. Food that was absolutely delicious the night before suddenly gets this terrible reputation the next day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Economic Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/new-economic-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/new-economic-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anyone knows that material wealth is measured in goods: apples, cars, shoes, sheep, etc. When the number and the quality of these things increases, wealth increases.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Pain No Gain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/no-pain-no-gain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/no-pain-no-gain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the early years of our community, we all actively participated in fun runs. The more serious runners would often say, &amp;ldquo;No pain, no gain.&amp;rdquo; I was sometimes amazed at the amount of discipline some athletes exercised in order to excel in their sport. Hours of every day would be taken up with developing physical fitness, speed, and endurance. To excel, they had to learn to push through what was called &amp;ldquo;the pain barrier&amp;rdquo;. But when they succeeded, they would come out on the other side as winners.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prayer Meetings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/prayer-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/prayer-meetings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(This is a Bible study, so you will need to look up the references in parentheses if you want to get the full meaning of this article.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prevericating</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/prevericating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/prevericating/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Prevaricating is defined as: &amp;ldquo;speaking evasively; equivocating&amp;rdquo;. And equivocating is defined as: &amp;ldquo;using vague or intentionally evasive language&amp;rdquo;. Whichever term you choose to use for it, there is a lot of this that goes on in the world today, and it happens far too often in our community as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality in Utopia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/reality-in-utopia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/reality-in-utopia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Utopia is an ideal world that does not exist. People searching for such a place often abandon ideals altogether when they fail to find it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Servants of The Antichrist</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/slaves-of-the-antichrist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/slaves-of-the-antichrist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;Left Behind&lt;/em&gt; series is inspiring, in that it makes people think about serious, life-and-death situations. Yet it tends to assume that, even in the face of disaster, life for fundamentalist American Christians will center around the same values and goals that have dominated their lives up until now. In other words, people will still go to church on Sundays and work in system jobs the rest of the week, right through the Tribulation and all that comes with it. They will still be loaded with money, and they will still jet around the world at will. There is nothing in the book that speaks to the condition of poor Christians. This materialistic philosophy is practised at a time (in the story) when people should be seriously considering whether the values they lived by before the trouble began were really the right ones.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Sense</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/sexs-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/sexs-sense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Opinions, experiences, customs, and beliefs about sex differ so much that almost nothing can be said dogmatically on the subject. Yet this is an area where dogmas abound&amp;hellip; from restrictive religious dogmas to permissive liberal dogmas (e.g. &amp;ldquo;Nothing is wrong if it makes you feel good&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs of The Times</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/signs-of-the-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/signs-of-the-times/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;War and Peace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wars are the most common proof given that the end of the world is near. Yet they are mentioned specifically by Christ as proof that the end has not come: &amp;ldquo;You will hear of wars and rumours of wars. Do not let this trouble you, for all these things must happen, but the end is not yet.&amp;rdquo; (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=Matthew&amp;#43;24%3A6;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read Matthew 24:6&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;Matthew 24:6&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Salvation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/simple-salvation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/simple-salvation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A member of The Family (formerly the Children of God) commented that he found it difficult to understand how we could consider them heretics and our best friends at the same time. Heretic is not a word that we would choose, because it has so much emotional judgment attached to it. But it is true that we have differences, at the same time that we have much in common; and we too have laboured to understand this paradox. The next five articles compare our similarities and difference on a number of teachings.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smile, God Loves You!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/smile-god-loves-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/smile-god-loves-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a greater sin than not obeying Jesus; it is the sin of not believing that he loves you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So, You Want to Start Your Own Ministry?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/you-want-to-start-your-own-ministry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/you-want-to-start-your-own-ministry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;People often write to us who are not satisfied with what they see in the churches today, and so they want to start their own ministry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solid As A Rock</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/as-hard-as-a-rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/as-hard-as-a-rock/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It has not been easy for people to build a case against us and our teachings for one very important reason: We have built our faith on the most solid foundation anyone could ever choose for any religion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Without Spice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/space-without-spice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/space-without-spice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article is a continuation of a topic which has been coming up a lot in the past couple of years. It deals with the dilemma that exists when a leader (or the community as a whole) encounters someone who shows some good spiritual signs, but who also shows an unwillingness to deal with some particular weakness or fault. Our traditional approach has been to take a grievance with the offender, and to advance the grievance from first stage to second, to third, and finally to kick them out of the community if they continue their refusal to deal with the offence. The process is scriptural and beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surely, Not All Evil</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/surely-not-all-evil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/surely-not-all-evil/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;St. Paul wrote a letter to a young Christian, and said that the root of all evil is the love of money. (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=1&amp;#43;Timothy&amp;#43;6%3A10;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read 1 Timothy 6:10&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;1 Timothy 6:10&lt;/a&gt;) This is an amazing claim.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take Up the Press and Follow Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/take-the-press-and-follow-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/take-the-press-and-follow-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The secular media has been around for a long time. Before newspapers and television it was the far less reliable word-of-mouth. It was this secular medium that crucified Jesus. The same crowd that shouted &amp;ldquo;Hosanna!&amp;rdquo; one week was shouting &amp;ldquo;Crucify him!&amp;rdquo; the next.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teach Others To Teach Others</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/teach-others-to-teach-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/teach-others-to-teach-others/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Study to show yourself approved unto God, a workman that needeth not to be ashamed, rightly dividing the word of truth.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=2&amp;#43;Timothy&amp;#43;2%3A15;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read 2 Timothy 2:15&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;2 Timothy 2:15&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Day The Earth Stood Still</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-day-the-earth-stood-still/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-day-the-earth-stood-still/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On our flight back to Sydney from Kenya on the weekend, Cherry and I watched a movie called &amp;ldquo;The Day the Earth Stood Still&amp;rdquo; (a remake of a film that first came out decades ago). I was deeply impressed with it in several ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fear of the Devil</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-fear-of-the-devil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-fear-of-the-devil/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most religions promote fear of the devil. But what you fear is what you worship. If you are afraid of the devil, he need only say, &amp;ldquo;X is evil!&amp;rdquo; and you will run from X. Obviously, he is going to make sure that what you run away from is exactly what you need to face.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forsake All Principle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-forsake-all-principle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-forsake-all-principle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a principle in spiritual matters that people from many faiths have discovered. We call it the &amp;ldquo;forsake all&amp;rdquo; principle. But it could be described in many other ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gift of Prophesy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-gift-of-prophesy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-gift-of-prophesy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some concerns are more understandable, and more honest, than others. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Golden Thread</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-golden-thread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-golden-thread/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a vision that was very strong and that seemed significant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Good Hindu</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-good-hindu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-good-hindu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A religious man asked Jesus, &amp;ldquo;What can I do to have eternal life?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Escape</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-great-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-great-escape/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a difficult story to tell, and that probably explains why it has taken some fifteen years for us to get around to telling it. The difficult part is not telling the story, but the difficult part is the fact that we have always shied away from giving testimonies about miracles, because of what the Bible says about evil people wanting miracles and not being content just less sensational truth. We also know that it can be somewhat discouraging to hear miraculous accounts from other Christians when our own lives seem so unexciting by comparison. We should start by saying that this story is probably one of the top three stories of God&amp;rsquo;s provision over a period of 35 years of Christian service. (Maybe one day we will get around to telling the other two!)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hollywood Scam</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-hollywood-deception/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-hollywood-deception/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-hollywood-scam&#34;&gt;The Hollywood Scam&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://jesuschristians.com/images/Article_pics/Article_Intro_Pics/Endtime_and_Sex/The_Hollywood_Scam.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It has been about forty years since Hollywood first took the leap into nude sex scenes in movies, and it may be time to look back on how that has influenced our thinking about such things.  I am going to argue in this article that many of us have been coyed into believing that there was something right and good about the decision to incorporate nude sex scenes into mass entertainment, when, in fact, it actually exposed (and continues to expose) us as naive suckers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Intuition Myth</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-intuition-myth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-intuition-myth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a term that I have heard for many years and just kind of assumed I was missing something when I heard it. The word is intuition. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how it has been used in the past, but I know that I mostly hear it used when comparing males and females. Females are told that they have intuitive skills, or that they think intuitively, whereas men think in some other way, e.g. rationally. Unless I&amp;rsquo;ve missed something, it always seemed to imply two things, both of which I would like to challenge in this article: (1) that intuition is some kind of a skill; and (2) that women have some kind of a special claim on this skill.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kingdom of Heaven or Religion</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-kingdom-of-heaven-or-religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-kingdom-of-heaven-or-religion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We wanted to know the important differences between the Christian religion and all other religions; between the part of the Bible before Jesus was born, and the part after he was born, between the teachings of Jesus and the teachings of all other religious leaders. We were not interested in the small differences that most people argue about. We asked God to show us the important differences, and he did.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Love of Selfie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-love-of-selfie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-love-of-selfie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;But know this, that in the last days perilous times will come: 2 For men will be lovers of themselves, lovers of money, boasters, proud, blasphemers, disobedient to parents, unthankful, unholy,&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=2&amp;#43;Timothy&amp;#43;3%3A2;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read 2 Timothy 3:2&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;2 Timothy 3:2&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mark of the Beast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-mark-of-the-beast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-mark-of-the-beast/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The last book of the Bible is called The Revelation by Protestants and The Apocalypse by Catholics. It is a poetic description of the battle between good and evil, using numerous symbols and creatures to illustrate its message.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Reason</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-reason/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-reason/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;_It is enough for the disciple that he be as his master, and the servant as his lord. If they have called the master of the house Beelzebub, how much more shall they call them of his household? &lt;a href=&#34;http://jesuschristians.com/bible/B40C010.htm#V25&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=Matthew&amp;#43;10%3A25;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read Matthew 10:25&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;Matthew 10:25&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;_&lt;br&gt;&#xA;It is becoming harder and harder for us to convince people that we are just another (safe) religious group.  Sooner or later they hear that there is a lot of nasty stuff being said about us, and with google being so handy these days, the question comes sooner rather than later: i.e. &amp;ldquo;Why is everyone saying such nasty stuff about you?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Revolution</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-revolution/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a Bible study.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please look up the verses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Slippery Slope</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-slippery-slope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-slippery-slope/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We had a discussion last night and Jeremy rightly said, &amp;ldquo;I can see an article coming from this.&amp;rdquo;  We were discussing the concept of a  &amp;ldquo;slippery slope&amp;rdquo; in our Christian walk, and we came up with a number of interesting observations.  The argument I am referring to is the one that says a certain action or teaching is likely to lead to much worse actions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Spirit of Christ</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-spirit-of-christ/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-spirit-of-christ/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Christian tradition has tended to exaggerate the distinction between the Son of God and God&amp;rsquo;s Holy Spirit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tentmaking Myth</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-tent-making-myth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-tent-making-myth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Catholics, Evangelicals, Pentecostals, High and Low Church Anglicans, Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s Witnesses, the Children of God, Mormons - in fact, every denomination and sect we know of - has one belief in common: they all support the tentmaking myth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The True Conscience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-true-conscience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-true-conscience/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: The term &amp;ldquo;social conscience&amp;rdquo; as used in this article has a different meaning (within the Jesus Christian community) to that which it normally has in society. We are talking about giving in to pressure from society to behave in certain ways which may actually be contrary to what a genuine conscience might teach us. An example of this would be social pressure to participate in war, which can make a sincere conscientious objector feel &amp;ldquo;guilty&amp;rdquo; for not conforming. We are NOT referring to &amp;ldquo;social conscience&amp;rdquo; in the way it is normally used (i.e. to feel a need to help others who are in need). That kind of social conscience is something with which we would agree.It has struck me that I must have failed somewhere in my attempts to teach people to recognise and follow what we call our conscience.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Virgin Army</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-virgin-army/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-virgin-army/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The seventh chapter of The Revelation (about the army of 144,000 people) has, like so much of The Revelation, been ignored by most Christians on the basis that it could be misinterpreted by fanatics to make them think they are part of the army and others are not. How silly!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Forty Commandments of Jesus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-top-forty-commandments-of-jesus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-top-forty-commandments-of-jesus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;1. Obey my commandments - &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=John&amp;#43;14%3A15;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read John 14:15&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;John 14:15&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=John&amp;#43;14%3A21;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read John 14:21&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;John 14:21&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=John&amp;#43;14%3A23;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read John 14:23&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;John 14:23&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=2&amp;#43;John&amp;#43;6;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read 2 John 6&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;2 John 6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try The Spirits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/try-the-spirits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/try-the-spirits/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(This study is written in Easy English.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many times when we must judge other people, and say if we believe they are right or if we believe they are wrong.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Right They&#39;re Wrong</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/were-right-theyre-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/were-right-theyre-wrong/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Within our community, we try to use the Golden Rule &amp;ndash; measuring our actions by the same principles that we use for measuring the actions of our enemies, and vice versa. So if, for example, we want freedom to distribute our literature, then we believe that they should have the same freedom. If it is wrong for them to cause division in our ranks, then we must not deliberately set out to cause division in their ranks. And so on and so on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Would False Jesus Do?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/what-conterfiet-jesus-would-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/what-conterfiet-jesus-would-do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a slogan making the rounds in church circles (especially in the U.S.) which asks &amp;ldquo;What would Jesus do?&amp;rdquo; It is abbreviated WWJD? and the letters feature on everything from T-shirts to jewellery. They act both as a reminder to the person wearing them and as an opening to a Christian witness when the uninformed ask what they stand for.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why So Much Persecution?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/why-so-much-persecution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/why-so-much-persecution/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The following article quotes William Penn, an early Quaker, with regard to persecution. Modern Day Quakers are highly respected around the world; but there was a time when they, like the Jesus Christians, were sorely persecuted for their faith.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisdom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/wisdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/wisdom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A number of children&amp;rsquo;s stories tell of someone getting one or more wishes, and then wasting them on things that do not bring happiness. As a boy I had heard the story of Solomon being given a wish by God. (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=2&amp;#43;Chronicles&amp;#43;1%3A7-12;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read 2 Chronicles 1:7-12&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;2 Chronicles 1:7-12&lt;/a&gt;) It was not so different from the fairy tales, except that this one had a ring of truth about it. What a privilege it would have been to be given a wish by God! And how clever of Solomon to have asked for wisdom.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Without Guile</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/without-blemish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/without-blemish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the article which follows, the Jesus Christians take a favorite Quaker passage of scripture (about &amp;lsquo;walking in the light&amp;rsquo;) and combine it with some of the favorite evangelical &amp;lsquo;salvation&amp;rsquo; scriptures, to present what is a favorite Jesus Christian teaching&amp;hellip; about sincerity. Several articles follow which also emphasise the need to be honest in preference to any theological demands. Such inclusivism is common to Quakers and Jesus Christians.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
