<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deep Thoughts on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/categories/deep-thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deep Thoughts on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/categories/deep-thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Character</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/character/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/character/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What ever happened to good old-fashioned character?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The world is full of friendly, polite, helpful&amp;hellip; outwardly very nice people. But in the midst of adversity, when &amp;rsquo;niceness&amp;rsquo; is really needed, how much remains?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Science</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/christian-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/christian-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the book Life After Life, a doctor interviews hundreds of people who were clinically dead and then revived. He notes a number of patterns in their experiences. One of these patterns was a widespread conviction by many of these people as they were dying that what really matters in life is not how much money you earn, but how much you love others and how much you learn.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fasting Without Ceasing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/fasting-without-ceasing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/fasting-without-ceasing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This kind goeth not out, except through prayer and fasting. (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.biblegateway.com/passage/index.php?search=Matthew&amp;#43;17%3A14-21;&amp;amp;version=50;&amp;amp;interface=print&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; title=&#34;Read Matthew 17:14-21&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&#xA; &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&gt;Matthew 17:14-21&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Say It</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/just-say-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/just-say-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There really is nothing wrong with what the &amp;ldquo;sinner&amp;rsquo;s prayer&amp;rdquo; says, even though we have tended to put it down in the past. And getting people to actually say the things that are said in the sinner&amp;rsquo;s prayer is a very good exercise. I just wish that we could get them to continue saying those things. Our complaint about the prayer is more that it tends to become a once-and-for-all ritual, that exempts people from continuing to grow in their faith.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The True Conscience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-true-conscience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-true-conscience/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: The term &amp;ldquo;social conscience&amp;rdquo; as used in this article has a different meaning (within the Jesus Christian community) to that which it normally has in society. We are talking about giving in to pressure from society to behave in certain ways which may actually be contrary to what a genuine conscience might teach us. An example of this would be social pressure to participate in war, which can make a sincere conscientious objector feel &amp;ldquo;guilty&amp;rdquo; for not conforming. We are NOT referring to &amp;ldquo;social conscience&amp;rdquo; in the way it is normally used (i.e. to feel a need to help others who are in need). That kind of social conscience is something with which we would agree.It has struck me that I must have failed somewhere in my attempts to teach people to recognise and follow what we call our conscience.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Right They&#39;re Wrong</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/were-right-theyre-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/were-right-theyre-wrong/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Within our community, we try to use the Golden Rule &amp;ndash; measuring our actions by the same principles that we use for measuring the actions of our enemies, and vice versa. So if, for example, we want freedom to distribute our literature, then we believe that they should have the same freedom. If it is wrong for them to cause division in our ranks, then we must not deliberately set out to cause division in their ranks. And so on and so on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
