<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Theology on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</title>
    <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/tags/theology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Theology on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/tags/theology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/amazing-grace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/amazing-grace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is easy to assume that people have already heard about God&amp;rsquo;s grace through the churches. But on closer inspection, it appears that the churches themselves do not believe the gospel they preach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>God Has No Grandchildren</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/god-has-no-grandchildren/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/god-has-no-grandchildren/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We do not have to be perfect to be accepted by God. But we do need to be original.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head Coverings</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/headcoverings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/headcoverings/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There have been whole denominations that have split over varying interpretations of one chapter of the Bible, which is: 1 Corinthians 11. This is the chapter that deals with women covering their heads when they pray.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Say It</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/just-say-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/just-say-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There really is nothing wrong with what the &amp;ldquo;sinner&amp;rsquo;s prayer&amp;rdquo; says, even though we have tended to put it down in the past. And getting people to actually say the things that are said in the sinner&amp;rsquo;s prayer is a very good exercise. I just wish that we could get them to continue saying those things. Our complaint about the prayer is more that it tends to become a once-and-for-all ritual, that exempts people from continuing to grow in their faith.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living By Faith</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/live-by-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/live-by-faith/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the third in a series of articles on doctrinal differences between ourselves and The Family. The first two articles were &amp;ldquo;Simple Salvation&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Eternal Salvation&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miracles</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/miracles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/miracles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you understand how a miracle works, is it still a miracle? If I can do something you have no explanation for, does that make me spiritually superior to you? What is a miracle anyway? These are just a few of the questions which have perplexed me as I have tried to understand what my position should be with regard to the supernatural.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Salvation</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/simple-salvation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/simple-salvation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A member of The Family (formerly the Children of God) commented that he found it difficult to understand how we could consider them heretics and our best friends at the same time. Heretic is not a word that we would choose, because it has so much emotional judgment attached to it. But it is true that we have differences, at the same time that we have much in common; and we too have laboured to understand this paradox. The next five articles compare our similarities and difference on a number of teachings.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fear of the Devil</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-fear-of-the-devil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-fear-of-the-devil/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most religions promote fear of the devil. But what you fear is what you worship. If you are afraid of the devil, he need only say, &amp;ldquo;X is evil!&amp;rdquo; and you will run from X. Obviously, he is going to make sure that what you run away from is exactly what you need to face.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Golden Thread</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-golden-thread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/the-golden-thread/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a vision that was very strong and that seemed significant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Without Guile</title>
      <link>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/without-blemish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgakristiyanonghesus.github.io/en/blog/without-blemish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the article which follows, the Jesus Christians take a favorite Quaker passage of scripture (about &amp;lsquo;walking in the light&amp;rsquo;) and combine it with some of the favorite evangelical &amp;lsquo;salvation&amp;rsquo; scriptures, to present what is a favorite Jesus Christian teaching&amp;hellip; about sincerity. Several articles follow which also emphasise the need to be honest in preference to any theological demands. Such inclusivism is common to Quakers and Jesus Christians.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
