<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Churches and Theology on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/categories/churches-and-theology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Churches and Theology on Mga Kristiyanong Hesus</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/categories/churches-and-theology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Grace</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/amazing-grace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/amazing-grace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is easy to assume that people have already heard about God&amp;rsquo;s grace through the churches. But on closer inspection, it appears that the churches themselves do not believe the gospel they preach.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living By Faith</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/live-by-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/live-by-faith/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the third in a series of articles on doctrinal differences between ourselves and The Family. The first two articles were &amp;ldquo;Simple Salvation&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Eternal Salvation&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miracles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/miracles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/miracles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you understand how a miracle works, is it still a miracle? If I can do something you have no explanation for, does that make me spiritually superior to you? What is a miracle anyway? These are just a few of the questions which have perplexed me as I have tried to understand what my position should be with regard to the supernatural.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Salvation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/simple-salvation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/simple-salvation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A member of The Family (formerly the Children of God) commented that he found it difficult to understand how we could consider them heretics and our best friends at the same time. Heretic is not a word that we would choose, because it has so much emotional judgment attached to it. But it is true that we have differences, at the same time that we have much in common; and we too have laboured to understand this paradox. The next five articles compare our similarities and difference on a number of teachings.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fear of the Devil</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-fear-of-the-devil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-fear-of-the-devil/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most religions promote fear of the devil. But what you fear is what you worship. If you are afraid of the devil, he need only say, &amp;ldquo;X is evil!&amp;rdquo; and you will run from X. Obviously, he is going to make sure that what you run away from is exactly what you need to face.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Golden Thread</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-golden-thread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/blog/the-golden-thread/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a vision that was very strong and that seemed significant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
